Jesse Stone: Thin Ice is a drama, crime, tv movie
film directed by Robert Harmon.
Jesse Stone and Captain Healy are shot during an
unauthorized stake-out in Boston.
Meanwhile, a cryptic letter sent from Paradise leads the
mother of a kidnapped child to Stone.
Though her son was declared dead, she hopes he will reopen the case.
Jesse Stone, played by Tom Selleck.
Rose Gammon, played by Kathy Baker.
Luther 'Suitcase' Simpson, played by Kohl Sudduth.
Sidney Greenstreet, played by Leslie Hope.
Captain Healy, played by Stephen McHattie.
Gino Fish, played by William Sadler.
Jesse Stone: Thin Ice is a 2009 American made-for-television crime drama film directed by
Robert Harmon and starring Tom Selleck, Kathy Baker, and Kohl Sudduth.
Based on the characters from the Jesse Stone book series created by Robert B.
Parker, the film is about the police chief of a small New England town who investigates a cryptic
letter sent to Elizabeth Blue, the mother of a kidnapped child who was declared dead.
Filmed on location in Nova Scotia, the story is set in the
fictitious town of Paradise, Massachusetts.
Jesse Stone: Thin Ice is the fifth in a series of nine television films
based on the characters of Parker's Jesse Stone novels.
The film received an American Society of Cinematographers Award for Outstanding Achievement in Cinematography at the 2009 American Society of
Cinematographers Awards, as well as a Canadian Society of Cinematographers Award for Best Cinematography in TV Drama for Rene Ohashi.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.